edumantra.net 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy |

**[www.edumantera.net-](http://www.edumantera.net-/) Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy sets out how [www.edumantra.net](http://edumantra.net/) uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website.

WE are committed to ensure that your privacy is protected. We use your given information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Edumantra.net  may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from June 1st 2016.

 **Information Collection And Use**

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information

that can be used to contact or identify you-  

 **We may collect the following information:**

  * Name and job title
  * Contact information such as name, email, mobile number, phone number, street, city, state, pin code, country and IP address.
  * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers such as If you use our website, we may collect information about your IP address and the browser you’re using. We might look at what site you came from, duration of time spent on our website, pages accessed or what site you visit when you leave us. We might also collect the type of mobile device you are using, or the version of the operating system your computer or device is running.

 **We collect information in different ways.**

 **We collect information directly from you.** We collect information directly from you when you register for an event or buy tickets. We also collect information if you post a comment on our websites or ask us a question through phone or email.

 **We collect information from you passively.** We use tracking tools like Google Analytics, Google Webmaster, browser cookies and web beacons for collecting information about your usage of our website.

 **We get information about you from third parties.** For example, if you use an integrated social media feature on our websites. The third party social media site will give us certain information about you. This could include your name and email address.

 **What we do with the information we gather**

 **We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons**

 **We use information to contact you:** We might use the information you provide to contact you for confirmation of a purchase on our website or for other promotional purposes.

 **We use information to respond to your requests or questions.** We might use your information to confirm your registration for an event or contest.

 **We use information to improve our products and services.** We might use your information to customize your experience with us. This could include displaying content based upon your preferences.

 **We use information to look at site trends and customer interests.** We may use your information to make our website and products better. We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties.

 **We use information for security purposes.** We may use information to protect our company, our customers, or our websites.

 **We use information for marketing purposes.** We might send you information about special promotions or offers. We might also tell you about new features or products. These might be our own offers or products, or third-party offers or products we think you might find interesting.

We use information as otherwise permitted by law.

 **Sharing of information with third parties**

 **We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf.** We share information with vendors who help us manage our online registration process or payment processors or transactional message processors. Some vendors may be located outside of India.

 **We will share information with the event organizers.** We share your information with event organizers and other parties responsible for fulfilling the purchase obligation. The event organizers and other parties may use the information we give them as described in their privacy policies.

 **We will share information with our business partners.** This includes a third party who provide or sponsor an event, or who operates a venue where we hold events. Our partners use the information we give them as described in their privacy policies.

 **We may share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves.** We will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may also share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. Or, we might also share information when we are investigating potential fraud.

 **We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business.** For example, if part of our business is sold we may give our customer list as part of that transaction.

 **We may share your information for reasons not described in this policy.** We will tell you before we do this.

 **Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

 **Google Adsense**

The ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

 **Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

 **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that Website privacy policy other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

 **Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at edumantra.[net@gmail.com](mailto:edumantra.net@gmail.com)

 **Taking care of your Password/s( Password security)** :

www.edumantra.net firmly believes in protecting the personal information of the customer. [www.edumantra.net](http://edumantra.net/) or any of its staff or official will never ask for any password or related information from its customers and the customers are also advised, in order to protect access to their accounts and to other channels, do not disclose the passwords to anyone. Generally the default password will be generated by system administrator and once it is received by you, you are requested to change the same and have your own password. It is recommended that the customers necessarily choose their own passwords carefully such that no unauthorized access is made by a third party. The customers are also advised not to keep any written or other record of the password/s so that no third party could access the same. The customers will also need to undertake not to disclose the password to anyone. In order that the passwords become complex and difficult for others to guess the you should carefully choose the alpha numeric passwords with combination of upper case alphabets and numbers and special characters.( like @,%,&,! etc.)  The password is private information and must be kept confidential by the owner of the username related to the password. If a password is known by someone other than the owner, that username and password could be misused to access resources and information possibly with criminal intent—and without notice since they would appear as the registered owner.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

 **  Changes To This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of June1; 2016 and will remain in effect except with respect to any Changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your Consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

 **Jurisdiction**

If you choose to visit the website, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and the website’s terms of use. In addition to the foregoing, any disputes arising under this Policy shall be governed by the laws of India.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: www.edumantra.net

SCO- 499 Ground Floor, Ganesh Colony, Sreet no.- 7, City- Chandausi, Dist. Sambhal State- U.P. 244412 (India)

edumantra.net@gmail.com
